{
    "subject": "resource/Bob_Corritore",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1956",
    "human_readable": "Bob Corritore was born in 1956.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9013410210609436,
            "question": "In what year was Bob Corritore born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8231863379478455,
            "question": "Where was Bob Corritore born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.797734260559082,
            "question": "What significant events happened in the year Bob Corritore was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6188576221466064,
            "question": "Is Bob Corritore a famous person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.607944130897522,
            "question": "What is the significance of Bob Corritore's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.548879086971283,
            "question": "What is Bob Corritore known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4104747474193573,
            "question": "What is Bob Corritore's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4032680094242096,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Bob Corritore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39995917677879333,
            "question": "Has Bob Corritore made any notable contributions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3168477714061737,
            "question": "Where does Bob Corritore live now?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bob Corritore was born in 1956.",
            "html": "dbpedia_894_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Bob Corritore made any notable contributions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_894_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting facts about Bob Corritore?",
            "html": "dbpedia_894_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Bob Corritore's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_894_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_894_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_894_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_894_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_894_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_894_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_894_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_894_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_894_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_894_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_894_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}